18stream.com 2011-01-20

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  

**Our Commitment To Privacy Your privacy is important to us.**  
To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.   
To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

**The Information We Collect:**  
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on website. On some pages, you can order products/subscriptions, make requests, and register to receive materials.   
The types of personal information collected at these pages are:  
\- Names  
\- Addresses  
\- Email addresses

**The Way We Use Information** is to ship product, send out verification of orders placed, and retrieve lost passwords.  
We reserve the right to contact you by e-mail in order to inform you about status of your order and give some recommendations if your subscription fails.

**Our Commitment To Data Security:**  
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information:**  
You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by using your account information at Segpay's website. You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before  
granting access or making corrections.

**How To Contact Us:**  
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at: support@18stream.com   

© 2010 18stream.com
